(intro beaming)
(creepy music)
(gentle music)
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Bye bye bye ♪
♪ Bye bye ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm doing this tonight ♪
♪ You're probably gonna start a fight ♪
♪ I know this can't be right ♪
♪ Hey, baby, come on ♪
♪ I loved you endlessly ♪
♪ When you weren't there for me ♪
♪ So now it's time to
leave and make it alone ♪
♪ I know that I can't take no more ♪
♪ It ain't no lie ♪
♪ I wanna see you out that door ♪
♪ Baby, bye bye bye ♪
♪ Bye bye ♪
♪ Don't wanna be a fool for you ♪
♪ Just another player
in your game for two ♪
♪ You may hate me but it ain't no lie ♪
♪ Baby, bye bye bye ♪
♪ Bye bye ♪
♪ Don't really wanna make it tough ♪
♪ I just wanna tell you
that I've had enough ♪
♪ It might sound crazy
but it ain't no lie ♪
♪ Baby bye bye bye ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ You just hit me with the truth ♪
♪ Now girl you're more than welcome to ♪
♪ So give me one good reason ♪
♪ Baby come on ♪
♪ I've lived for you and me ♪
♪ And now I really come to see ♪
♪ That life would be much
better once you're gone ♪
(Justin laughing)
♪ I know that I can't take no more ♪
♪ It ain't no lie ♪
♪ I wanna see you out that door ♪
♪ Baby, bye bye bye ♪
♪ Bye bye ♪
♪ Don't wanna be a fool for you ♪
♪ Just another player
in your game for two ♪
♪ You may hate me but it ain't no lie ♪
♪ Baby, bye bye bye ♪
♪ Bye bye ♪
♪ Don't really wanna make it tough ♪
♪ I just wanna tell you
that I've had enough ♪
♪ Might sound crazy but it ain't no lie ♪
♪ Baby, bye bye bye ♪
♪ I'm giving up I know for sure ♪
♪ I don't wanna be the reason
for your love no more ♪
♪ Bye bye ♪
♪ I'm checking out, I'm signing off ♪
♪ I don't wanna be the
loser, and I've had enough ♪
♪ I don't wanna be your
fool in this game for two ♪
♪ So I'm leaving you behind ♪
(car screeching)
(JC blowing)
(upbeat music)
♪ I don't wanna make it tough ♪
♪ Make it tough ♪
♪ But I've had enough ♪
♪ And it ain't no lie bye ♪
♪ Bye bye, baby ♪
♪ Don't wanna be a fool for you ♪
♪ Just another player
in your game for two ♪
♪ I don't wanna be your fool ♪
♪ But it ain't no lie ♪
♪ Baby, bye bye bye ♪
♪ Bye bye ♪
♪ Don't really wanna make it tough ♪
♪ I just wanna tell you
that I've had enough ♪
♪ It might sound crazy
but it ain't no lie ♪
♪ Baby, bye bye bye ♪
♪ Bye bye ♪
♪ Don't really wanna make it tough ♪
♪ I just wanna tell
you that I had enough ♪
♪ Might sound crazy but it ain't no lie ♪
(cars screeching)
(cars humming)
♪ Bye bye bye ♪
♪ Bye bye ♪